希望泰德喜欢吃三文鱼
Oh, I hope Tad likes salmon.
第一次来邓菲家做客
It's a bit of a risk serving fish
就给他吃鱼还是挺有风险的
to a first-time diner at Dunphy's.
要不我还是腌块牛排做候补吧
Maybe I should marinate a steak for backup.
有人好像爱上某男了哦
I think someone has a man crush.
首先 我绝不会和未来的客户约会
First of all, I would never date a potential client.
你该先澄清一下性取向吧
That's "First of all"?
其次 此次晚餐必须顺利进行
Secondly, I really need this to go well
那样他才会选我做房产经纪人 那家伙炒房地产
so he makes me his realtor. This guy's flipping properties
堪比功夫电影中令人炫目的动作
like they're extras in a kung fu movie.
所以你是为了钱才猛拍他马屁吗
So you're just kissing up to this guy for his money?
不仅仅是钱 我真的喜欢他
Not just. I really like him.
他周游各国 乐善好施
He travels the world doing charity work,
会攀岩 会开飞机
rock climbs, flies planes...
他怎么有时间做那么多事啊
How does he have time to do all that?
他离婚了 于是开辟了新的人生
Got divorced, and his whole life opened up.
他简直过着梦一般的生活啊
Guy's living the dream.
他的梦
His dream.
不是我的梦 我的梦想就在这里
Not my dream. I'm living my dream.
你就是我的美梦
You're my dream.
少来这套
You can stop.
我真心不想做这个
I so don't want to do this.
最近 海莉在她的
Recently, Haley got a little creative
某张大学申请表上突发奇想
on one of her college applications
说自己是一名"大姐姐"
and listed herself as a "Big Sister."
严格地说 我本来就是家中大姐姐
Technically, I am a big sister.
她把"大"和"姐"都突出强调
She capitalized the "B" And the "S."
倒也说得通 那组织就是假"大"虚空 贱"姐"无数
Which makes sense, 'cause it was.
所以克莱尔和我建议
So Claire and I suggested--
是强迫
Forced.
她去大哥哥大姐姐会做志愿工作
that she volunteer for the organization.
我们为她自豪得不行了
We couldn't be prouder.
其实可以
We could.
再自豪一点的
Little bit.
老爸
Hey, dad?
是你不小心把这本专门嘲笑律师的
Did you accidentally leave this hilarious book
笑话书落在客房的吗
Of lawyer jokes in the guest room?
要是你能问答以下问题 我就告诉你
I'll tell you if you can answer the following question--
一条鲶鱼和一名律师
What's the difference between
-二者的区别是什么 -不知道 是什么
- a catfish and a lawyer? - I don't know. What?
一个在烂泥里打混 靠榨取底层生物过活
Well, one's a bottom-feeding mud-dweller.
另一个则是一条鱼
The other's a fish.
犀利
zing!
正中目标
Honk!
好了各位 晚餐已经好了
Okay, everyone, dinner is served!
准备开饭吧
let's get it!
我们的房子正在消毒 所以杰和歌洛莉亚
Our house is being fumigated, so Jay and Gloria
邀请我们回娘家住几天
invited us to stay here for a few days.
我真高兴能和她一起共度72小时
I am very excited to have 72 hours with this one.
我们平时相处的时间很少
We don't get to spend much time together,
可以想象这几天我们会像是
so I know that we're gonna be like, um...
弗雷德和琴吉
Fred and Ginger?
谁啊
Who?
电影之夜
Movie night!
比平时要吵闹好几倍
It's nosier than usual around here.
我的娘啊
oh, gosh!
泰德 真是极品好酒啊
Tad, this wine is fantastic.
在门多萨呆上一周[阿根廷 盛产葡萄]
Spend a week in Mendoza,
你就会发现一堆马尔贝克酒生产商
and you'll find a dozen or so Malbec producers
可以酿出堪比波尔多酒的美酒佳酿
that'll give most Bordeaux a real run for their money.
抱歉
Mm. I'm sorry.
酒瓶上应该贴个警告
This should come with a warning--
"可能导致装逼说大话行为"
"May cause pretentiousness."
该贴警告标签的是你 "极品帅男 靠近危险"
You should come with a warning-- "May be fascinating."
-抱歉 -天啊
- Oh! Excuse me. -Oh, gosh!
该死的螺丝老是松出来 都第九次了
Oh, that's, like, the ninth time this screw has popped out.
那个 我需要一个直角螺丝刀
Oh, you know what? I need the angled screwdriver.
可我把它落在办公室了
I left it at the office.
我把它留在那是因为我的那些标记牌
I, um, I keep it there because of--of all my signs.
我用它来钉"待售"的牌子
I'll, uh, put up a "For sale" sign,
然后保证第二天
and next day, of course,
-我就会换上个"已售"的牌子了 -没错
- I gotta put up the "Sold" banner. - Yeah.
然后第三天 同样的情况 "待售"
Then the next day, same deal--"For sale"
"已售"
"Sold."
"待售——已售""待售——已售"
"For sale." "Sold." "For sale." "Sold."
你真是个很棒 很棒的推销员
You're a great-- great salesman.
-我明白了 -"待售——已售"
- I'm getting that. - "For sale." "Sold."
很好 那个 我得回家好让保姆下班了
Right. Listen, I-I-I gotta go relieve the babysitter.
我前妻带走了我一半的财产
My ex-wife took 50% of my stuff
却留下了所有的孩子
and left me 100% of my kids.
-孩子们很不错 - 我说
- They're great. Hey, listen, um,
非常感谢你的光临
thank you so much for coming.
哪里 我才要谢谢你 菲尔
Oh, no, thank you, Phil, so much
谢谢你们做的三文鱼 牛排
for the salmon and the steak
还有鸡肉和大虾
and the chicken and the shrimp.
每一样都很美味
I mean, it was all just delicious.
-太好了 -能有这样的贤妻 他真走运
- Oh, great. - This guy is very lucky to have you.
好 那就多谢了
Okay. Thanks.
没问题
Yeah.
好吧
All right.
-让我帮你开门 -行
- Let me grab that. -Yeah.
非常感谢 再见
Yeah. Thanks so much. Bye-bye.
再见
Bye-bye.
你看到那一幕没
Did you see that?
握手差点变成拥抱吗
A handshake that almost became a hug?
当然看见了 我是当事人啊 我成功了
Yeah, I saw it. I lived it. I think I'm in.
不 亲爱的 是他亲到我的嘴
No, honey. He kissed me on the lips.
-又一个好信号 -这不是什么好信号
- Another good sign! - It's not a good sign.
亲爱的 你不觉得这很古怪吗
Sweetie, you don't think that's weird?
那家伙满世界乱跑
Well, the guy's a world traveler.
他曾在哥斯达黎加呆过一段时间
He has a time share in Costa Rica.
也许是受那里的习俗影响吧
That's probably how they do it there.
我不知道 亲爱的 感觉他在我唇上流连忘返
I don't know, honey. It felt like he lingered.
人家是先进性文化嘛
It's a progressive culture.
出行都得靠索道滑行
Most of them travel by zip line.
饼干配肉汁
biscuits and gravy?
我奶奶贝奇的独家秘方
Yep, my grandma Bitsy's secret recipe,
从她管家黛丽拉那里学到的
given to her by her housekeeper Delilah,
她养大了我奶奶 也是她最好的朋友
Who raised her and was her best friend--
就像电影《相助》一样 除了黛丽拉是白人
kind of like "The help," except Delilah was white,
而且是个种族主义者
and was actually herself quite the racist.
放开肚子吃吧
Eat up.
早安
Good morning!
-早 妈妈 -早 亲爱的
- Hi, mom. - Hi, sweetheart.
这些花是哪儿来的啊
Ah, where did those come from?
没错 我以为朱顶红都开过季了呢
Yeah, I thought amaryllis were out of season.
我认识个熟人 我只是觉得
Oh, I got a guy. You know, I just thought
花能让家里看起来明亮一点
they'd brighten up the house a little bit.
你想得真是太周到了
Oh, that was so thoughtful of you.
我不觉得我家需要更明亮一点啊
I didn't realize that my house needed brightening up.
小公主来了
There she is!
歌洛莉亚 歌洛莉亚
Gloria! Gloria!
哎呀 让我来帮你修复一下发型
Ay! Let me fix your hair!
那真是有爱啊
Oh. Well, isn't that sweet?
我不觉得她的发型糟糕啊
I didn't realize her hair was broken.
闻起来好香啊
Ah! That smells delicious,
可我不能吃了 有个很早的工作午餐
but nothing for me. I've got an early work lunch.
是吗 我没听到救护车的声音啊
Really? I didn't hear an ambulance.
好好笑哦 因为我已献身于法律事业
Yeah, it's funny because it's what I've dedicated my life to.
是和那个名字很搞笑的DJ见面吗
Oh, is this that meeting with the deejay with the funny name?
布克·贝尔
Booker Bell.
-布克·贝尔 -布克·贝尔吗
- Booker Bell. - Booker Bell?
大家听好了
Everybody now!
布克·贝尔是史上最伟大的
Booker Bell was only the greatest deejay
交通台广播DJ
in the history of drive time radio.
他有几块湿地被开放商看上了
Yeah, well, now he has some wetlands that developers want,
我们希望让他捐给保护区
and we're trying to get him to donate for preservation.
我还在跑公路生意那会儿
When I was on the road selling,
总是听布克的广播呢
I used to listen to Booker all the time.
"整盅电话"差不多就是他发明的
He practically invented the prank phone call.
好了 祝我好运吧
Okay. Wish me luck.
好运哦 亲爱的
Good luck, sweetie!
布克会先搞一段恶作剧
Booker would play a prank,
那个倒霉蛋会被整得七窍生烟
the sucker would be twisting in the wind,
就在你忍无可忍的时候
and just when you couldn't stand it anymore,
他就会说 "猜猜整盅电话整到谁了"
he'd say, "Guess who just got their bell rung!"
老天 我真想见他一面
God, I'd love to meet him.
他们就约在雷记餐厅
Oh, they're just going down to Rae's.
你赶快飞奔过去吧
You should pop down.
-他见到粉丝肯定很开心 -我没想好
- I'm sure he'd love to meet a fan. - I don't know.
有一次去见波兹·斯加格斯 我话都说不利索了
I met Boz Scaggs once, got all tongue-tied.
噢 你可以的
Oh, you'll be fine.
糟糕 莉莉 亲爱的 该去学校了
Oh! Oh, Lily, it's time for school, sweetie.
我可以送她去啊
Oh, I can take her.
那就太谢谢你了
Oh. That'd be great.
我正好帮你收拾收拾厨房
Yeah, it'd give me some more time to clean the kitchen.
扫扫尘之类的
Maybe do a little dusting.
很好吃 小卡
Delicious, Cam.
安妮真棒 集风趣可爱贴心于一身
Annie was amazing, so funny and cute and sweet.
-要说几遍 -昨晚她画了幅画送我
- Yeah, you've said. - She made this for me last night.
瞧她的签名 "A"写得多萌啊 还打个卷儿
Look how she signs her name with that big loopy "A."
我得把它裱起来
I'm totally going to frame this.
4年前我也给海莉画过一张
I made this for Haley four years ago.
您觉得这张被裱起来了吗
You think this got framed?
她捏成团扔垃圾桶了
She tossed it in the garbage...
背面还写满了"海莉·乔纳斯三兄弟共有的夫人"
Right after she wrote "Mrs. Haley Jonas Brothers"
写了大概30遍
on it, like, 30 times.
光是税金减免就已经很诱人了
The tax write-off alone makes financial sense.
更别提对环境的诸多好处了
You know, even if you take the environment out of it.
别不提环境问题啊
Well, don't take the environment out of it.
没了湿地 就没了鸭子
Without the wetlands, there's no ducks,
没了鸭子 就没东西让我射着玩了
and without the ducks, there's nothing for me to shoot at.
好吧 虽然我们考虑的角度不同
Okay. Well, we're shooting from two different angles,
但希望最终能达成一致意见
but, uh, hopefully we'll end up at the same place.
-米奇 -爸
- Mitch. - Dad?
我忍不住过来跟他打个招呼
I just had to stop down and meet this guy.
布克·贝尔你好 我是波兹·斯加格斯
Booker Bell, I'm Boz Scaggs--
错了 我是杰·普里契特 妈的
No! I mean Jay Pritchett. Damn it.
-很高兴见到你 -真是太荣幸了
- It's nice to meet you. - This is such an honor.
你一直是我最喜欢的电台主持人
You are hands down my favorite radio personality of all time.
你真会逗人开心
That's kind of you to say.
好了 谢谢你特意过来一趟 爸
Okay. Well, thanks for stopping by, dad.
我得跟你聊件趣事
You know, I gotta tell you one thing.
回头我们在家里聊吧
I'll see you back at the house.
有次我从扬斯敦开往糖果河
One time when I was driving from Youngstown to Sugar Creek,
你给一个猫砂公司的人打去整盅电话
You called this guy at a kitty litter company
让他带900磅猫砂过去
and you asked him to bring over 900 pounds of litter,
当时背景音乐是一群狮子在咆哮
and in the background, you hear all these lions roaring, and...
我都快把肺笑出来了 差点出事
I-I laughed so hard, I almost had an cicident.
车出事还是人出事
The car or you?
你还是那么逗
Funny as ever!
-随便吧 -你跟老一帮的还有联系吗
- Anyway... - Hey, are you still in touch...with the old gang?
时髦奶奶 还有宇航员克莱德
Grandma groovy? Spaceman Clyde?
-开玩笑吗 老一帮就是我 -骗谁呢
- Are you kidding? I am the old gang. - No way.
我或许老了 但跳起布吉舞来毫不费力
I may be old, but I still know how to boogie.
天呐 简直如她亲临现场
My god, it's like she's here!
就是她啊
She is here!
你怎么还不明白呢
How are you still not getting this?
那角色就是他演的
That's her.
抱歉 一会就来
Excuse me for a sec.
你搞什么飞机啊
What are you doing?
咋了 我是他的粉丝 过来打个招呼而已
What? I'm a fan. I came down to say hi.
我们可是在进行工作会谈
This is a business meeting.
你完全没意识到很不合时宜吗
Do you have any idea how inappropriate this is?
当然 你肯定觉得无所谓
No. No, of course you don't,
因为在你看来 律师的工作不过是
because as far as you're concerned, all a lawyer does
走进法庭 面对法官 以及准备钓律师的白熊女
is walk into a bar with a rabbi and a polar bear.
是灰熊啦 不然的话 当酒保...
Grizzly, 'cause otherwise, when the bartender--
爸 我在工作
Dad! I'm working!
你是在丢我们父子两个人的脸
You're embarrassing both of us!
拜托您赶紧走吧
Please, you gotta go!
好吧 我没意识到那一点
All right. I didn't realize that.
没错 你是没有
Yeah. Yeah. You didn't.
抱歉 走吧
I'm sorry. Go.
我的疯狂粉丝呢
Hey. Where's my stalker?
他走了 终于摆脱他了
Oh, he's gone. I got rid of him.
他缠着你喋喋不休 真不好意思
Sorry that he attacked you like that.
缠着
Attacked?
没有的事 都习以为常了
No. I don't mind a little smoke up my bombers.
我只是觉得工作商谈是件正经事
Well, I just thought since this was supposed a business meeting.
我们应该
We should...
你觉得有个人让我心情愉快会
And you thought maybe having somebody make me feel good would
破坏商谈吗
wreck it?
我跟我爸的关系一直很紧张
There's--there's been a lot of tension between me and my dad.
我现在住在他家 所以有点
I'm actually staying at his house and it's just a...
所以你赶走一个为你敞开大门的人是吗
Oh, so you chased away a man who's opened his home to you?
我觉得我好像要搞砸了
I get the sense that I'm losing you.
我能跟时髦奶奶谈吗
Could I talk to Grandma Groovy?
亲爱的 我回来啦
Honey, I'm home!
这么早就回来了啊 亲爱的
Well, I didn't expect you so early, dear.
你怎么在啊
What? You?
看看谁来给咱家修桌子了
Yeah. Look who came by to fix the table.
我正好有些闲工夫
Well, I had some time to kill,
所以就顺道来给你老婆送修理工具了
so I thought I'd drop by with that tool your wife needed.
-真是个大好人啊 -没错
- Wow. What a guy. - Yeah.
他还带了酒哦
He also brought some wine.
昨晚你说你喜欢喝
Well, you said you liked it last night,
正好我家里有几瓶放着没人喝
so I had a couple extra bottles lying around.
老兄 女孩的心思都被你猜透了
Boy, do you know the way to this gal's heart.
我来不只是帮你家修桌子
I didn't just come here to fix your table
顺便把你老婆灌醉的
and get your wife drunk.
我其实是来告诉你
I actually decided to give you
由你来做我的房产经纪人
that listing on the sycamore property.
真的吗 太棒了
Really? That's great.
不如今晚到我家来吃晚饭吧
Yeah. Why don't you, uh, come over for dinner tonight?
我们可以谈谈细节 简单熟悉一下
And, uh, we'll work out all the details. One entree.
克莱尔 你也一起来吧
Claire, you should come, too.
不了 不了 你们谈生意
Oh, no, no. No, no, if it's business--
我强烈要求
I insist.
-盛情难却 我们会到的 -好吧
- He insists. We'll be there. We're coming. - Okay.
7点怎么样
Yeah, shall we say, uh, 7:00?
-7点可以 -说定了
- 7:00 sounds great. - Okay.
好的
All right.
-不用送了 -行
- I'll let myself out. - Okay.
惊了
Wow.
我也觉得很震惊
"Wow" Is right.
他说让我做经纪人
I just got sycamore--
那房子不用推销就能大卖 我白捡便宜了
A house that sells itself and gives me the commission.
你就一点都不在意吗
How does that not bother you?
克莱尔 我就那么一说
Claire, it's an expression.
还是要干活的啊 要检查房屋 估价
There's work. Inspections, appraisals--
他给我带酒
He brought me wine,
你不在的时候他把衬衫都脱了
He took his shirt off when you weren't here!
酒是带给咱俩的
Um, he brought us wine,
而且 桌子下面也确实有点脏嘛
and it doesn't look super vacuumed down there.
他该把裤子也脱了才对
I'm surprised he kept his pants on.
好了 好了 我明白怎么回事了
Okay. Okay, I can see what's going on.
你太专注于拉他当客户
You--you're just so focused on getting his business,
以至于你没看到事情的真相
that you don't see what's going on in front of you.
好的 我现在看清了
Okay. Now I do see what's going on.
-看清什么 -过来 美妞
- What? - Come here, pretty girl.
-咋了 -你很美 只是我不常说而已
- What? Mm? - You are, you know. You don't hear it enough.
那一晚 你着上淡妆
The other night, when you put on makeup,
我心里想 "我老婆真美"
I was like, "There she is."
我的天呐
Oh, my god.
你觉得我是虚荣心作祟才瞎编乱造的吗
You think I'm making this up as some part of a-an ego boost?
你知道这有多侮辱人吗
Do you realize how insulting that is?
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
帮我的小妹妹做作业
Helping my little sister with her homework.
你手段 真卑劣
That seems... Mean.
安妮 这位是艾丽克斯
Annie, this is Alex.
就是我跟你说过的另一个妹妹
That other sister I was telling you about.
你好 很高兴见到你
Hi. So nice to meet you.
如果你要在我的床上学习
Um, if you're going to study there,
还是把第7题到第10题答案改一下吧
You might need to correct numbers 7 through 10.
这张床的标准可比那张床高多了
This bed has higher standards than that bed.
我去再拿点柠檬水来
I'm going to get some more lemonade.
我觉得你姐姐生我们姐姐的气了
I think your sister's mad at our sister.
我们回来了
We're back!
终于回来了 我猜"吃完饭就回家"
Oh, well, there you are. I guess "Lunch then home"
对不同的人有不同的意思哈
means different things to different people.
我带着小美女逛街了 莉莉 快过来
We had a girls' day. Lily, Lily, come!
给你爸爸看看我们买什么了
Show your papa what we bought!
母女装
Matchy jackets!
她穿上就跟小豹子一样
It's like she's the baby leopard,
而我是母豹子哟
And I'm the mama.
或者就是两件普通的大衣
Or they just happened to have two jackets,
一件大号的 一件小号的
one large, one small.
抽屉里怎么了 我的茶哪去了
What happened here? Where is my tea?
茶在这边的抽屉里
Oh, it's in this drawer over here.
为了感谢你
As a thank-you,
我花了点时间把你家厨房重新打理了一下
I took some time to rearrange your kitchen
好有条理一些
So it makes sense.
对谁有条理
To who?
对所有人啊 现在有层次感了 看着
To everyone. There's a flow now. Watch--
茶 马克杯 茶壶 不用谢
Tea. Mug. Kettle. You're welcome.
我又没谢你
I didn't thank you.
你不必谢
You don't have to.
我没打算谢
I won't.
小卡 躲在我们的共用厕所里
Cam, our shared bathroom is not the place
可不是解决问题的办法
to work out whatever's going on here.
我是经历过父母离异的小孩
I'm a child of divorce.
化解冲突可算是我的专长
Conflict resolution is something of a specialty.
关键是 要跟当事人讲一个
The key is, tell a personal story
能引起他共鸣的故事
that applies to their situation,
就算现编也得编
even if you have to make one up.
那样的话 他们就会听到需要听到的道理
That way, they really hear what they need to hear.
抱歉 你说的对
I'm sorry. You're right.
不 抱歉我打扰到你了
No. I'm sorry I snapped.
我只是对我喜欢的一个女生
I'm just going through some stuff
有点想法 她叫丹妮尔
with this girl I like, Danielle.
她前几天来我家 而斯黛拉老粘着她
She came over the other day, and Stella was all over her,
然后 然后我就吃醋了
And--and I got jealous.
这有点不可理喻 对吧
Which is crazy, right?
我是说 斯黛拉和她玩只是一种新鲜感
I mean, Stella was only playing with her because she was new.
曼尼 听起来丹妮尔想
Manny, sounds like Danielle was trying
破坏你和你的小狗之间的感情
to get between you and your puppy,
性质很恶劣啊
And that ain't cool.
她好像很不成熟 而你可以找个更好的
She seems immature, and you can do better.
我很抱歉直言不讳
I'm sorry to be blunt,
但是我自己现在也在经历感情波折
But I'm going through something myself right now.
所以 振作点 好的
So, chin up. Okay.
虽然未必每次都管用
It may not work every time,
但你只需要搞定一位就可以了
but you only need one fish to bite.
那个丹妮尔是谁
Who is this Danielle?
她是我历史课上的学习搭档
She's my study partner in my history class,
我们共享笔记的
and we share a notebook.
但她的笔记比较混乱
But her notes were really confusing,
所以我将之列的井井有条的
so I put them in order.
而她非但不感谢我让学习变得更容易
Instead of thanking me for making our lives easier,
她还生我的气 因为她认为我在批评她
she got all mad because she thought I was judging her.
那个女生相当不靠谱 曼尼
This girl is very bad news, Manny.
你离她远远的
You stay away from her.
我们是菲尔和克莱尔
We're Phil and Claire.
我是 我是托尼
Hey, I'm Tony.
快进来 我去叫我爸爸
Come on in. I'll go get my dad.
-好的 -很好 谢谢
- Okay. - Great, thanks.
我不喜欢那孩子看你的方式
I don't like the way that kid was looking at you.
我们现在不是朋友
We are not friends right now.
我只是过来帮忙搞点给孩子们上大学的钱
I am only here to help pump up the college fund.
克莱尔 如果泰德对你毛手毛脚的
Claire, if Tad even makes a move towards you,
我就打的他屁股开花
His ass is... grass.
是吗 我以为只是我的虚荣心在幻想呢
Really? I thought that was just my ego.
目前 是的 但是你要明白
So far, yeah, but just know,
我已经准备好打得他屁股开花了
I'm ready to grass his ass.
嘿 两位
Hey, hey, hey, guys.
嘿 你好吗
Hey! How are you!
-很好 -很高兴见到你
- Good. - Good to see you.
-好啊 -这就行了
- Yeah. - Hi. That's good.
这房子不错啊 你重装修了吗
Well, I love the place. Did you remodel this?
事实上是我前妻搞的
Uh, actually, my ex-wife.
她那个 很热衷于现代建筑
She had a, uh, passion for modern architecture
以及至少一位现代建筑师
and at least one modern architect.
或许接下来也会把它卖掉
May have to sell this one next.
真的
Really?
我喜欢它的开放式结构
I love how open it is.
-你介意我 参观一下吗 -请便
- Do you mind if I, uh, poke around? - Please, yeah.
真漂亮
Beautiful.
泰德 如果你不需要我照看孩子了
Tad, if you don't need my help anymore with the kids,
-那我就走了 -太感谢你了 艾伦
- I'll be going. -Thank you so much, Ellen.
不客气
You're welcome.
好的 我们回头见 再见
Okay. We'll see you later. Bye.
我8年前见过这房子
I saw this house eight years ago.
这里以前有堵墙 对吧
There used to be a wall here, right?
对 对的 不过已经改掉了
That's right. That's right. That was all covered.
我可是很注重细节的 别想逃过我法眼
Yeah.I'm a detail guy. Hard to get much past me.
好啊 好啊
Hello, hello!
-你好 卡拉阿姨 -你好吗
- Hi, aunt Kara! - How are you?
我很好 泰德 你怎么样
Good, Tad, How you doing?
-拜 爸爸 -拜 亲爱的
- Bye, daddy. - Bye, sweetie.
-拜 老板 -好好玩
- Bye, dad. - Have fun.
好的 回头见
Okay. See you later.
快点孩子们 咱们走了
Come on, guys, let's go.
楼梯以前是柚木的 对吧
These stairs used to be teak, am I right?
你老公真厉害啊
This guy's good.
是啊 他是很厉害
Yeah, he's good.
-他非常犀利 -我忘拿包了
- He's sharp. - I forgot my bag.
你每次都这样
You do that every time.
没错
Yep.
我从来都不放过任何细节
I don't miss much.
抱歉 你是想看书吗
Oh, I'm sorry. Were you trying to read?
你想看也看不懂啊
You're the one who tries to read.
擦 你妹的 姐还没那么笨呢
Oh, my gosh! I am not that stupid!
说真的 海莉 你以为你是
Seriously, Haley, you think you
-有史以来最酷的人啊 -你能不能
- are the coolest person ever! - Would you please stop
别只要看见我干点啥就立马损我
just judging me and everything that I do?
"看看姐 姐好拽啊"
"Look at me! I'm so cool!"
够了 够了
Enough! Enough!
我真是受够你们每天在一起掐架了
I am so sick of you two fighting all the time!
你是个坏大姐
You're a bad big sister,
而你也不是什么好二姐
And you're a bad little sister!
反正都是我的坏姐姐
And you're both bad big sisters to me.
正常点吧
Be normaler.
我还没见过他这么发飙呢
I've never seen him like that.
我们确实有点忽视他的感受了
Well, we do kind of neglect him.
仔细想想吧
And if you think about it,
他有点像是 我们的小妹妹
he is kind of... our little sister.
还记得以前我们怎么打扮他的吗
Remember how we used to dress him up?
我想她
I miss her.
我听见你们了
I hear you,
而且我很不喜欢这对话的发展方向
and I don't like where this is going!
你负责拿口红
You get the lipstick,
我去拿胸罩和网球
I'll get the bra and tennis balls.
贝蒂·卢克
Betty Luke!
我会把这房子烧了的
I will burn this house down!
乳酪磨碎机哪去了
Where is the cheese grater?
那切菜板呢
Where is the cutting board?
你想让它在哪
Where would you want it to be?
是 就在乳酪磨碎机的旁边
Yes, right here next to the cheese grater.
我知道光看表面看不出来
I know it's hard to tell by looking at me,
但我真不是做主妇的料
But I am not a natural homemaker.
所以小卡对我的厨房整顿之后
So when Cam came and organized my kitchen,
我觉得失去了安全感 备受打击
I felt insecure and lashed out.
从某方面来说 我不比
In a way, I'm no better
曼尼那不可理喻的朋友丹妮尔好多少
than Manny's crazy friend Danielle.
拜托 我们能专心做菜吗
Please, can we just focus on the cooking?
爸爸 我们忘记给你这个了
Daddy, we forgot to give you this.
和我们的外套是一个系列哦
It's like our jackets.
我很喜欢
I love it.
我想我一直都对莉莉
I guess I've always been a little sensitive
没有妈妈的事情很敏感
about Lily not having a mother,
而歌洛莉亚很好地担当了这个角色
and Gloria's so good at it.
我有些吃醋
I got jealous.
也许我应该跟曼尼讲讲这个故事
Maybe I should tell Manny this story.
也许对他和那个灾星丹妮尔的事情有些帮助
It might help him with that train wreck Danielle.
你知道吗 何不重新打开音乐
You know what? Why don't you turn that music back on.
听起来很不错
Was kind of nice.
爸爸
Hey, dad...
你什么都不用说
No need to talk about it.
我突袭你们的商谈确实有点过分
I was out of line coming down there,
此类事情绝不会再发生了 酒在吧台上
won't happen again. Scotch is at the bar.
不 我想了很多
No, I've been giving this a lot of thought.
你大概又要拉着我谈心了
I guess we're gonna talk about it.
我对你太无礼了
I was rude to you.
我想我只是有点恼火那些调侃律师的玩笑
I think I was just annoyed by all the lawyer jokes.
坦白一点讲 你对我的工作
I mean, let's be honest, you don't exactly
并不引以为豪
beam with pride over what I do for a living.
常言道 讽刺是最真挚的奉承
Mockery is the sincerest form of flattery.
我很确信 常言中可没那个说法
Pretty sure that's-- that's not the saying,
不过 曼尼给我讲了一个
But, um, you know, Manny told me a story
关于他朋友丹妮尔的故事
about his friend Danielle.
顺便说一句 听上去她是个了不起的人物
She sounds like a real piece of work, by the way.
但是 那个故事让我意识到
But, uh, it made me realize that
我太把自己当回事了
I take myself a little too seriously.
听着 不用说我也一直都为你自豪
Listen, it goes without saying I've always been proud of you,
也一直到处吹嘘你
and I brag about you all the time.
所以如果我说 "律师用什么来避孕"
So if I say, "What do lawyers use as birth control?"
答案通常是"他们令人讨厌的性格"
And the answer is, "Their personalities,"
你要知道我不是指你
I want you to know I'm not referring to you.
因为你压根儿不需要避孕
You don't need any birth control.
你好
Hello?
是的 我是杰·普里契特
Yeah, this is Jay Pritchett.
什么 什么时候
What? When?
发生什么了
What happened?
是警察 我的车被偷了
It's the police. My car got stolen.
是的 2012 灰色
Yeah, 2012. Gray.
不 不是蓝灰色 更像是淡
No, not pewter. More like a light...
像是 不 不是暗蓝色
Like a--no, not slate.
我都不知道"雾灰色"是个什么色
I don't even know what "Coastal fog" Is.
写"灰色"就行了
Just put down "Gray."
奇洛吗
Kilo?
那不是我的车
It's not my car.
对 她是哥伦比亚人
Yes, she's columbian.
和这个有什么关系 不 我现在下去
What does that have to do with--no, I'm coming down there.
等等 带上钥匙
Hang on. Grab your keys.
我想我需要个律师
I think I might need a lawyer.
猜猜整盅电话整到谁了
Guess who just got his bell rung?
完全骗到他了
That's good.
真有两下子
来吧 请坐
Here we go. Have a seat.
我有一瓶1899年的波尔图葡萄酒
I got a bottle of port from 1899.
好吧 其实是18.99美金的葡萄酒
Okay, I got it for $18.99...
不过是瓶好酒
but it's a good one.
-今晚很棒 晚餐也很棒 -对吗 是的 而且
- Fun night, right? Great dinner? - Yes. Yes, and...
泰德是个大好人
Tad is... great,
我知道我之前有些难为你
and I know I was giving you a hard time...
但我觉得我应该说声对不起
But I feel like I should say that I am sorry.
克莱尔 你不用解释
Hey, hey, hey, Claire, you don't need to explain.
你肯道歉已经让我受宠若惊了
Your apology is apology enough.
在哥斯达黎加的那个故事
Oh, I forgot the best part
我忘记讲最棒的部分了
of the Costa Rica story.
我们回家后 它们占据了客厅
So we get home, and they've taken over the living room,
占据了厨房
they've taken over the kitchen,
食物上 床上 到处都有它们的身影
I mean, they're in the food, they're on the bed.
终于 向迪亚戈抱怨了两年后
And finally, after two years of complaining to Diego about this,
他终于停止了 他说
he finally stops and says,
"好吧 现在我亲眼看到了
"Okay, now I see it.
你确实遇上猴群作乱了"
You do have a monkey problem."
猴群作乱
A monkey problem!
知道 他第一次说我就听清了
Yeah, I heard him the first time.
你可以亲吻我的妻子 可以和她滚床单
You can kiss my wife, you can take her to bed,
但是你不能逗她笑
but you cannot make her laugh.
我要重来一遍
I wanna go back.
你可以亲吻我的妻子
You can kiss my wife,
但只有我能和她滚床单和逗她笑
But only I can take her to bed and make her laugh.
我要再来一遍
I wanna go back.
只有我可以和我的妻子滚床单
Only I can take my wife to bed,
逗号
comma,
和逗她笑
and make her laugh.
它们真的无处不在
I mean, they're in everything.
它们唯一没有碰的东西
The only thing they didn't touch--
居然是香蕉
the bananas.
猴子爱香蕉
The monkeys love bananas!
天下哪有不爱香蕉的猴子
You would think they would love the bananas.
对 我们该走了
Yeah, we should go.
-没开玩笑吧 香蕉 -我们该走了
- Come on. The bananas-- - Yeah, we need to go.
-我们该走了 -不不
- We gotta get going. - Oh, no, no, no.
-时间太晚了 -但是他刚刚打开
- Yeah, yeah, we're late. - But he just opened the--
-我们回家要晚了 -谢谢你的盛情款待
- We're late for getting home. - Thanks for everything. Just--
你有什么毛病
What is wrong with you?
你笑得花枝乱颤 像是说"谁先上我"
You laughed like it was "Who's on first?"
什么
What?
他必须第二个上 别哄我
He's on second. Don't try to cheer me up.
我知道了 你吃醋了
I know what's going on here. You're jealous.
吃他的醋吗
Of him?
他一点都不好笑
He's not even funny!
他有什么 棍又软 时又短吗
What's he got? Like, a soft ten minutes?
而且他去哥斯达黎加的故事
And he goes to the Costa Rican well
我的品位完全无法理解
a little too much for my taste.
天呐
Oh, god.
不是吧 还在笑猴子吗
Really? This is still about the monkey?
不不不
No! No, no, no!
是你 你现在让我很开心
It's you. You are making me so happy right now.
你仓皇地逃出来了 简直像个傻子
You stormed out of there, and you're acting like an idiot.
你喜欢吗 我真的相当不爽
You like this? Because I am really uncomfortable.
亲爱的 我太喜欢了 让我觉得倍受重视
Honey, I love it. Makes me feel special.
有时候 我真的搞不懂你在想什么
Sometimes, I really don't understand you.
我知道 有点傻
I know. It's stupid,
但是看到你为我而战感觉很好
but it's nice to know that sometimes you'll fight for me,
而我只用对其他男人的故事笑笑就能看到
and all I have to do is laugh at some other guy's story.
但没有人能像你那样让我开怀大笑
But no one makes me laugh like you do.
只要这句永远是真的
As long as it's always genuine.
你的一切都可以是假的
You can fake anything you want with me,
只要笑容是真的就行
But not your laugh.
-我要重说一遍 -好
- I'd like to go back. - Yeah.
住手 走开
Stop it! Leave me alone!
-老实点 - 别动
- Hold still! - Stop moving!
我恨你们 走开
I hate you! Get off of me!
干什么呢你们
What... is going on?
你们有大麻烦了
You guys are in a lot of trouble.
海莉 我告诉过你把客厅收拾好
Haley, I told you to clean this mess up,
艾丽克斯 你的书丢得到处都是
And, Alex, your books are everywhere.
贝蒂·卢克娃娃 坐下来 你爸快去拿相机
Betty Luke, sit down while your dad gets the camera.
收到
Got it.
上次 你做了个鬼脸
Last time, you made a funny face
所以我们没有拍到一张很好的照片
and we didn't really get a good shot,
所以我们要练习微笑
so let's work on our smile.
好 见到你真高兴 贝蒂·卢克娃娃
Okay. Good to see you, Betty Luke.